<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
        <title>US Corruption</title>
        <description>US Corruption - Citizens For Justice</description>
        <link>http://uscorruption.github.io</link>
        <link>http://uscorruption.github.io</link>
        <lastBuildDate>2016-11-06T19:57:23-06:00</lastBuildDate>
        <pubDate>2016-11-06T19:57:23-06:00</pubDate>
        <ttl>1800</ttl>


        <item>
                <title>Pedo Ring Busted</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;OK, so it started out with finding out that a place called “Besta Pizza” which happens to be 2 doors down from Comet Ping Pong (owned by James Alefantis, who is the former gay boyfriend of David Brock). Besta Pizza has a logo that not only resembles the symbol for pedo/boy love but IS the symbol for pedo boy love.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;website here:
mybestapizza.com
&lt;a href=&quot;http://archive.is/3OrGh&quot;&gt;http://archive.is/3OrGh&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Logo here:
&lt;a href=&quot;https://sli.mg/WFX7jx&quot;&gt;https://sli.mg/WFX7jx&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FBI doc showing the symbols:
&lt;a href=&quot;https://sli.mg/00qA8D&quot;&gt;https://sli.mg/00qA8D&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then anon on 4chan tracked down who owned Besta Pizza (which BTW means “Beast” in portuguese)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://boards.4chan.org/pol/thread/96371913&quot;&gt;http://boards.4chan.org/pol/thread/96371913&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;here is the text from that:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ok I’m digging for ownership info and have found it - 
Uptown Pizza LLC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://sli.mg/0imhDH&quot;&gt;http://sli.mg/0imhDH&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I Found it by being more (?) specific with search terms. Just uptown or pizza would not return a result&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://sli.mg/NVNyV4&quot;&gt;http://sli.mg/NVNyV4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;LLC Business Filing - &lt;a href=&quot;http://sli.mg/A45Xa5&quot;&gt;http://sli.mg/A45Xa5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s signed by Andrew Kline, and it’s running on a revoked entity status.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Agent Address - 1225 19th Street N.W., Washington, DC 20036&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Andrew Klines listed address leads back to a palms restaurant - WTF - Currently needs digging&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also listed on the report is the following –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Governor: Hammad, Abdel Rahman 5029 Connecticut Ave., N.W., Washington, DC 20008 Is Executing Officer?: No - 
This the address of Besta Pizza.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So then I google Andrew Kline and Podesta - Bingo!
Turns out Andrew Kline knows Podesta AND is a Clinton appointee and “as one of four attorneys in the Human Trafficking Prosecution Unit of the Department of Justice, in the Civil Rights Division”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://archive.is/dFoRq&quot;&gt;http://archive.is/dFoRq&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So that means that the guy who owns a pizza place that uses a pedo symbol for it’s logo is in charge of finding human trafficking in the US at DOJ and was appointed by Clinton.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GET THIS TO THE FBI!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>http://uscorruption.github.io/doj/2016/11/06/pedo-ring-busted</link>
                <guid>http://uscorruption.github.io/doj/2016/11/06/pedo-ring-busted</guid>
                <pubDate>2016-11-06T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Assange is Dead, March on DC</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;The shitposting needs to stop if you are going to save your government. This story is the only thing you need to be talking about if you truly want to see justice. FBIAnon wanted you to see this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fbi.gov/investigate/terrorism&quot;&gt;https://www.fbi.gov/investigate/terrorism&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Definitions of Terrorism in U.S. Code 
18 U.S.C. § 2331 defines “international terrorism” and “domestic terrorism” for purposes of Chapter 113B of the U.S. Code, entitled “Terrorism.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“International terrorism” means activities with the following three characteristics:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Involve violent acts or acts dangerous to human life that violate federal or state law;
Appear to be intended  &lt;br /&gt;
(i) to intimidate or coerce a civilian population;  &lt;br /&gt;
(ii) to influence the policy of a government by intimidation or coercion; or   &lt;br /&gt;
(iii) to affect the conduct of a government by mass destruction, assassination, or kidnapping; and
Occur primarily outside the territorial jurisdiction of the U.S., or transcend national boundaries in terms of the means by which they are accomplished, the persons they appear intended to intimidate or coerce, or the locale in which their perpetrators operate or seek asylum.*&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First the Email in Question: &lt;a href=&quot;https://wikileaks.org/podesta-emails/emailid/7243&quot;&gt;https://wikileaks.org/podesta-emails/emailid/7243&lt;/a&gt; (Note it was Published on 10/13/16)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;At the same time we should return to plans to provide the FSA, or some group of moderate forces, with equipment that will allow them to deal with a weakened ISIL, and stepped up operations against the Syrian regime. This entire effort should be done with a low profile, avoiding the massive traditional military operations that are at best temporary solutions. While this military/para-military operation is moving forward, &lt;strong&gt;we need to use our diplomatic and more traditional intelligence assets to bring pressure on the governments of Qatar and Saudi Arabia, which are providing clandestine financial and logistic support to ISIL and other radical Sunni groups in the region.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is hard evidence that the US destabilized Africa in order to get Clinton elected. This is how Secretary Clinton empowered ISIS. Assange outlines how Clinton committed Treason, not &lt;em&gt;merely&lt;/em&gt; Pay-to-Play:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/_sbT3_9dJY4?t=4m16s&quot;&gt;Now pay attention because it is far more subtle and not nearly as inflammatory as American audiences would like.&lt;/a&gt; (Dartmouth Films). Clinton knew that Saudi Arabia and Qatar were arming ISIS while Secretary of State and they still gave weapons to Saudi Arabia and Qatar though we knew them to fit the FBI’s definition of Terrorism (This is what FBIAnon was talking about). This is “giving aid and comfort” to an enemy of the state, &lt;em&gt;by using the state department&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.heritage.org/constitution/#!/articles/3/essays/119/treason&quot;&gt;Heritage.org sites the US Constitution defining Treason&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Treason against the United States, shall consist only in levying War against them, or in &lt;strong&gt;adhering to their Enemies, giving them Aid and Comfort.&lt;/strong&gt; No Person shall be convicted of Treason unless on the Testimony of two Witnesses to the same overt Act, or on Confession in open Court.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;ARTICLE III, SECTION 3, CLAUSE 1&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before anyone criticizes to say its RussiaToday propaganda: It was produced by Dartmouth Films, a UK film company, and sold to broadcasters outside of the UK, RT being one of them. He talks about Wikileak’s criticism of Russia anyways. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rt.com/news/365405-assange-pilger-full-transcript/&quot;&gt;Full transcript available&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This brings us to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-34131911&quot;&gt;The Refugee Crisis&lt;/a&gt; (BBC) in Europe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Korea is forcing President Park Geun-hye to flee for her life for similar accusations &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.reuters.com/article/us-southkorea-politics-idUSKCN12T08V&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;right now&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;-(Rueters). Can we at least get a march going?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-34131911&quot;&gt;The Refugee Crisis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are a liberal ask yourself how you feel about and if you want to be the one defending it for &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2016/oct/31/refugees-problem-europe-identity-crisis-migration&quot;&gt;the next 40 years&lt;/a&gt; because this mass migration taking place in Europe is the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.npr.org/2015/12/27/461173027/reflecting-on-a-year-of-europe-s-migrant-crisis&quot;&gt;biggest thing to happen there since WW2&lt;/a&gt;. The memory of this wound will not fade quickly, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_association_football_rivalries&quot;&gt;if soccer has taught me anything&lt;/a&gt;, its that Europe is good at holding a grudge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is bigger than if Trump had &lt;em&gt;in fact&lt;/em&gt; shot someone on 5th avenue. &lt;strong&gt;Europe is going to be pissed&lt;/strong&gt;. Anticipate anti US marches in Berlin, Paris and London. This is 200 french concert goers getting murdered by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cnn.com/2015/12/08/politics/amnesty-international-isis-weapons-u-s-/index.html&quot;&gt;ISIS with American weapons&lt;/a&gt; leading to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nytimes.com/2015/05/06/world/europe/french-legislators-approve-sweeping-intelligence-bill.html&quot;&gt;Frances own version of the Partiot Act&lt;/a&gt;. This is evidence that the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/691638/Germany-migrant-crisis-immigration-economy-trillion-pounds&quot;&gt;TRILLIONS&lt;/a&gt; of dollars being spent on refugees in all of Europe is a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/congress/senate-poised-to-override-obama-veto-of-911-legislation/2016/09/28/809fd2a4-854b-11e6-b57d-dd49277af02f_story.html&quot;&gt;bill to set at the feet of America&lt;/a&gt;. This is why &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cbsnews.com/pictures/isis-attacks-a-timeline-of-terror/19/&quot;&gt;Charlie Hebdo&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nytimes.com/2015/11/15/world/europe/isis-claims-responsibility-for-paris-attacks-calling-them-miracles.html&quot;&gt;Bataclan&lt;/a&gt; were attacked. This is how &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nytimes.com/2016/03/23/world/europe/brussels-airport-explosions.html&quot;&gt;Brussels was bombed.&lt;/a&gt; This is why the the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.abc.net.au/news/2016-06-27/mccann-brexit-could-be-just-the-beginning/7545664&quot;&gt;UK left the EU&lt;/a&gt;. This is why hundreds of women in &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nytimes.com/2015/12/20/world/europe/norway-offers-migrants-a-lesson-in-how-to-treat-women.html&quot;&gt;Scandinavia&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.reuters.com/article/us-europe-migrants-germany-idUSKCN0S02N220151006&quot;&gt;Germany&lt;/a&gt; are being raped and assaulted. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/2016/07/turexit-turkey-leave-nato-160721105010182.html&quot;&gt;This is why Turkey may leave NATO&lt;/a&gt;. This is why &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cnn.com/2014/09/04/world/europe/uk-nato-summit/index.html&quot;&gt;Russia&lt;/a&gt; may invade the rest of Ukraine. This is why Trump wants to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2016/jan/04/donald-trump-great-again-first-campaign-ad-isis-mexico-wall-muslim-ban&quot;&gt;build a wall&lt;/a&gt;. Assange did not over-hype &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rt.com/news/319797-syria-depopulation-refugees-assange/&quot;&gt;the ramifications of US involvement in Syria.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stop waiting for CNN to confirm how damaging this is. Remember Shepherd Smith talking about Hurricane Mathew? You dont need that. This is enough if you want it; you need to assemble and march and take your country. This is it. This is all you get. The revolution will not be televised. Nor will it be there to incite your passions. Stoke the fires of justice in yourself. You need to march on DC today. TODAY. IS SOUTH KOREA MORE PATRIOTIC THAN AMERICA!? THEN GET OUT THERE AND SHOW YOU LOVE YOUR COUNTRY FOR [redacted] SAKE!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;marchondc-julianisdead&quot;&gt;#marchonDC #JulianIsDead&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its worth noting that nothing in this video suggests Assange is safe in the Embassy. Watch it again and you may see the edit where you dont see Pilger ask the question about the FBI investigation and Assange only makes a statement about the purpose of the FBI. Also Pilger makes a statement about the last week of the campaign and Assange never addresses that statement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;freejulian&quot;&gt;#freeJulian&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got banned for “Spam” after being instructed by a mod (Who I dont believe intended to get me banned) to repost the content into another thread. 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://np.reddit.com/r/WikiLeaks/comments/5b8pf0/assange_clinton_is_a_cog_for_goldman_sachs_the/d9moh78/?context=3&quot;&gt;https://np.reddit.com/r/WikiLeaks/comments/5b8pf0/assange_clinton_is_a_cog_for_goldman_sachs_the/d9moh78/?context=3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I didnt spam that sub. This is hitting hard guys. Please for the love of all that is Kek, share this:&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>http://uscorruption.github.io/assange/2016/11/06/assange-is-dead</link>
                <guid>http://uscorruption.github.io/assange/2016/11/06/assange-is-dead</guid>
                <pubDate>2016-11-06T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
        </item>


</channel>
</rss>
